<MAIN>
	<page imageDir="heidis_fudge/">
		<!-- Four Hundred Sketches -->
		<row css="header" bgColor="#DDD5CA" columnPadding="30" marginBottom="13">
			<col align="top" float="left" stack="none">
				<img src="purple_shield.jpg"/>
			</col>
			<col span="2">
				<txt><br/><h1>Tasty Packaging</h1><p></p><br/>
				<p>Heidi makes incredibly delicious fudge that wins the loyalty of everyone who tries it. However, in a retail environment consumers rarely have the luxury of sampling the fudge before purchase. Therefore, the brand and package needed to be every bit as compelling as the actual fudge. Just a few years after launching their new brand and packaging, Heidi’s Fudge has opened their own physical store and seasonal mall locations.</p></txt>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row css="h_fudge_row" bgColor="#2B221F" >
			<col>
				<txt><br/><h1>Market Research and Ideation</h1><p>We enjoyed logo exploration for Heidi’s Fudge more than usual. The restrictions were less rigid and Heidi supplied several samples for “market research.” With a slightly feminine dash of whimsy, we landed on the swirl as a fun metaphor referencing aroma, home cooking and melted chocolate.</p></txt>
			</col>
			<col float="right">
				<img src="sketches_new.jpg"/>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row css="description,h_fudge_light" bgColor="#2F2520" columnPadding="0" marginTop="17" marginBottom="17">
			<col stack="vertical">
				<txt><p><br/><br/>First round presentation sketches.</p></txt>
			</col>
			<col span="2" align="left" stack="horizontal" stackPadding="20">
				<img src="direction1.jpg" />
				<img src="direction2.jpg" />
				<img src="direction3.jpg" />
			</col>
		</row>
		<row bgColor="#DDD5CA" >
			<col>
				<txt><br/><h1>More than a box of chocolate</h1><p>We utilized techniques like embossing, die-cuts and self-adhesive stickers to their fullest. They provide the finishing touches to the Heidi’s Fudge brand, minimize production cost even make hand-packing more efficient. For customers, the boxes set a high expectation worthy of special occasions.</p></txt>
			</col>
			<col float="right">
				<img src="fudge_close.jpg" />
			</col>
		</row>
		<!-- <row bgColor="#DDD5CA" padding="">
			<col>
				<txt><br/><h1>Simple e-commerce</h1><p>While the packages were being fabricated, we developed promotional materials and a simple e-commerce web site. We coupled a playful attitude with simple, direct information.</p></txt>
			</col>
			<col float="right">
				<img src="browsers.jpg" />
			</col>
		</row> -->
	</page>
</MAIN>