<MAIN>
	<page imageDir="ibex/">
		<row marginBottom="-20" css="ibex_head,white" columnPadding="110" padding="0">
			<col span="3" >
				<img src="top.swf" yMod="-12" float="left"/>
				<txt yMod="45" xMod="20"><br/><h1>The Need</h1>
				<p>Overthrow an established competitor by creating</p> 
				<p>THE BRAND for truckers and corporate agents.</p></txt>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row>
			<col>
				<txt><h1>Naming Becomes Visual</h1><p>From 300+ naming possibilities, Ibex surfaced as the strongest solution both linguistically and visually. The name stands alone as an icon, but using a burly Himalayan mountain goat in the trademark clinched it.</p></txt>
			</col>
			<col float="right" span="2">
				<img src="sketches.jpg" />
			</col>
		</row>
		<row totalColumns="2" css="padded">
			<col></col>
			<col>
				<txt xMod="-30"><h1>Brand Development</h1><p>With Ibex, we sought to balance the masculine characteristics from the name with a more sophisticated, corporate appeal. Exploration allowed us to create an aggressive, rugged icon with enough polish to approach multi-national oil corporations.</p></txt>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row marginBottom="-140">
			<col float="left">
				<img src="truck.jpg" />
				<img src="logos.swf" yMod="-140" xMod="30"/>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row totalColumns="2" marginBottom="20" marginTop="20">
			<col>
				<txt>
					<h1>Branding for Visibility</h1><p>Trucks and drivers are the most visible link to Ibex. We designed trucks and uniforms to position the company on a daily basis. Invoices, reports and paper work provide the primary link for office personnel, so we created user-friendly, branded materials to establish Ibex as the preferred vendor.</p>
				</txt>
			</col>
		</row>
		<row totalColumns="2" marginTop="50" css="padded">
			<col>
				<img src="brochure.jpg" />
			</col>
			<col>
				<img src="jacket.jpg" />
			</col>
		</row>
		<row totalColumns="2" css="padded">
			<col>
				<txt>
					<h1>Making the Sale</h1><p>Only a handful of corporate presentation materials were created as leave-behinds for potential clients. The folders reinforce a sales presentation, yet acts as a stand alone brochure for managers higher up the approval chain.</p>
				</txt>
			</col>
			<col>
				<txt>
					<h1>For what it’s worth...</h1><p>Just after launch, IBEX received a telling request from one competitor’s long-time employee. The driver supplied his jacket and asked to have the Ibex logo embroidered, whatever the cost. He just liked the logo.</p>
				</txt>
			</col>
		</row>
		
	</page>
</MAIN>